<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life | Academic</title>
    <link>https://example.com/category/life/</link>
      <atom:link href="https://example.com/category/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <description>Life</description>
    <generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <image>
      <url>https://example.com/media/icon_hu0b7a4cb9992c9ac0e91bd28ffd38dd00_9727_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url>
      <title>Life</title>
      <link>https://example.com/category/life/</link>
    </image>
    
    <item>
      <title>How was my week</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/week-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/week-4/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-python&#34; data-lang=&#34;python&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;kn&#34;&gt;import&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nn&#34;&gt;libr&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nb&#34;&gt;print&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;hello&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;🌟 The past week at the university was full of bright events and important moments!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;fitness-aerobics-competitions&#34;&gt;Fitness aerobics competitions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The beginning of the week was marked by student competitions in fitness aerobics within the framework of the ICSI. The participants showed not only a high level of physical fitness, but also enthusiasm, energy and team spirit. Each team presented unique compositions combining elements of aerobics with modern dance moves. 💃🕺
🏆 We were able to successfully complete our program and took 2nd place. It is worth noting that this was our debut performance!!!
📚&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;test-work&#34;&gt;Test work&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the middle of the week, I came across another side of university life — a test paper on mathematical analysis. It was a serious test of the strength of knowledge and the ability to apply theoretical knowledge in practice. 📝&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;results&#34;&gt;Results&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Overall, the past week has been filled with both sports enthusiasm and academic tension. She showed that university life is not only about studying, but also active recreation, the development of sports skills and communication in a team. 🎓
👏🎓
👏&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How was the last week of April</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/week-22-28.04/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.com/post/week-22-28.04/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;highlight&#34;&gt;&lt;pre tabindex=&#34;0&#34; class=&#34;chroma&#34;&gt;&lt;code class=&#34;language-python&#34; data-lang=&#34;python&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;kn&#34;&gt;import&lt;/span&gt; &lt;span class=&#34;nn&#34;&gt;libr&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;line&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;cl&#34;&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;nb&#34;&gt;print&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;(&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;s1&#34;&gt;&amp;#39;hello&amp;#39;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;p&#34;&gt;)&lt;/span&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;p&gt;My last week consisted of studying, training and watching the preparations for the Victory Day parade.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;study&#34;&gt;Study&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Last week I studied new topics in mathematical analysis and mathematical logic, dealt with algorithms and solved interesting problems. There were many practical works that helped to deepen knowledge and skills in the field of information technology.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;fitness-aerobics-training-as-part-of-the-national-team&#34;&gt;Fitness aerobics training as part of the national team&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In addition to studying, I spent time training. This is a great way to keep fit and recharge your batteries for the whole day. There were a lot of funny moments in training that will definitely be recalled more than once in the future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;going-to-the-parade-rehearsal&#34;&gt;Going to the parade rehearsal&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The final, but no less important event of the week was my trip to the rehearsal of the Victory Day parade. It was a truly impressive event. The Victory Parade is one of the most significant and honorable events in Russia dedicated to the memory of the heroes of the Great Patriotic War.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;















&lt;figure  &gt;
  &lt;div class=&#34;d-flex justify-content-center&#34;&gt;
    &lt;div class=&#34;w-100&#34; &gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;&#34; srcset=&#34;
               /post/week-22-28.04/%D1%80%D0%B5%D0%BF%D0%B5%D1%82%D0%B8%D1%86%D0%B8%D1%8F_hu32ee5142eafcf9670e9d30251c1d7dde_133696_22fbc0d05bcce1cbcabaf76b232c6cea.webp 400w,
               /post/week-22-28.04/%D1%80%D0%B5%D0%BF%D0%B5%D1%82%D0%B8%D1%86%D0%B8%D1%8F_hu32ee5142eafcf9670e9d30251c1d7dde_133696_d46c14869e857d7d02ff74b637349cde.webp 760w,
               /post/week-22-28.04/%D1%80%D0%B5%D0%BF%D0%B5%D1%82%D0%B8%D1%86%D0%B8%D1%8F_hu32ee5142eafcf9670e9d30251c1d7dde_133696_1200x1200_fit_q75_h2_lanczos.webp 1200w&#34;
               src=&#34;https://example.com/post/week-22-28.04/%D1%80%D0%B5%D0%BF%D0%B5%D1%82%D0%B8%D1%86%D0%B8%D1%8F_hu32ee5142eafcf9670e9d30251c1d7dde_133696_22fbc0d05bcce1cbcabaf76b232c6cea.webp&#34;
               width=&#34;656&#34;
               height=&#34;438&#34;
               loading=&#34;lazy&#34; data-zoomable /&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
  &lt;/div&gt;&lt;/figure&gt;
&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Watching the parade rehearsal, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t help but admire the careful preparation of the military units, the skill and coordination of the participants. Military equipment, soldiers in uniform, musicians - everything created a unique atmosphere of celebration and memory.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was amazed by the greatness and heroism of those who participated in the parade. Seeing it all live was incredibly exciting and touching. Every step, every melody called for the preservation of the memory of the great victory and respect for those who gave their lives for our future.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I am proud to be a spectator at such a landmark event and once again felt how important it is to remember and honor the exploits of our ancestors. I hope that each of us will be able to pass this story on to future generations and keep the memory of the great Victory in the hearts of every person.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;lets-sum-up-the-results&#34;&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s sum up the results&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thus, the past week has been eventful and interesting. Useful time is spent both studying and training, as well as with pleasant emotions.
The time was spent usefully, I was energized for the next week!!!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
